question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                      "question": "'Santa Claus' is a variety of melon.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "SCP-173 was the first SCP article written for the web-based collaborative fiction project known as the 'SCP Foundation'",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "'Typewriter' is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The French word to travel is 'Travail'", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                      "question": "'Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.' is a grammatically correct sentence.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                      "question": "Furby was released in 1998.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Fast food restaurant chains Carl's Jr. and Hardee's are owned by the same company.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
